What a lovely picture, Piglet.
小猪   你画的画好美
You know, your blue lines remind me of something.
你知道吧   这些蓝色线条让我联想起一些东西
If only I could put my finger on it?
我可以把手指放上去吗
It looks like you already have your finger on it, Pooh.
维尼   你手指都已经放上去了好吧
Look.
快看
The map's got the same wavery lines as Picasso's painting.
图纸和毕加索的画好像诶
Oh, that's how I draw water, the lines are wavy so that looks like the waters are moving.
我就是这样画河流的   要画成曲线河流才会看起来是动态的
You see?
对不对
Water?
河流吗
Then the blue ones on the map must be picture of: The River!
那图纸里的蓝色线一定是河流啦
And this must the bridge!
那这肯定是小桥啦
Yeah, if we cross it, we've be even closer to the treasure!
对呀   我们要是穿过小桥   我们肯定会离宝藏更进一步的
Come on, everybody!
大家快走吧
Aye, aye. Captain Blue.
好的   蓝蓝首领